Roby Morgan

28/10/1987

Thereses gate 16H 0452 Oslo. (+47) 48504137 roby.c.morgan@gmail.com

PERSONAL PROFILE

I am currently exploring a new line of work. I have worked as a chef for ten years. I have learnt a lot of valuable skills working in the restaurant business which I can apply to working in any new field.

I am a fast learner, great at working in teams and a hard worker.

CURRENT EMPLOYMENT

Tiffany's Bjølsen, Oslo Norway

Started in October 2020, Part-Time position

EXPERIENCES AS A CHEF

Australia, France and Norway — Head Chef, Sous Chef, Apprentice

Kitchen management, design and prepare dishes, ordering and receiving produce.

Bar Tjuvholmen - Oslo

June 2020 - September 2020

The Under Ground Golf Club - Oslo

February 2020 - April 2020

Trancher Entrecote - Oslo

April 2015 - February 2017

Yaya's Thai Restaurant - Oslo

September 2013 - January 2015

Chalet One - St Foy Tarentaise, France

December 2012 - April 2013

Footscray Milking Station - Melbourne, Australia

May 2012 - September 2012

La-citta - Melbourne, Australia

Apprenticeship

EDUCATION

Galileo Maritime Academy, Phuket — STCW 2010 Basic Safety Course ²⁰¹⁹

eot.edu.au, Online training
— White card

FS Learning, Mornington — Certificate 3 In Hospitality

2011

Completed Certificate 3 In Hospitality Commercial Cookery

Princes Hill Secondary College, Princes Hill — VCE

Graduated 2006 VCE Year 11 and 12.

REFERENCES

Björn Johansson - Owner of Tiffany's Bjolsen +47 98909798

Matias Kolari - Head Chef BAR Tjuvholmen + 47 40744042

Olle Frandsen - Owner of The Underground Golf Club +47 90078097

Leonardo Alvarados - Current Head Chef + 47 90745990

David Pierre-Humbert - Tintuppa landscape. +61 423747212

Shannon Raftery - SCR landscape.

6 ways Bistro - Melbourne, Australia

Apprenticeship

Kin. Melbourne

Apprenticeship

OTHER WORK EXPERIENCES

Tintuppa Landscape, Rosebud, Victoria Australia — *Garden Maintenance*

January 2019 - September 2019

SCR Landscape, Stockdale Personnel, Victoria Australia — *Landscape labourer*

October 2018 - December 2019

Järvsöbacken, Sweden, Järvsö — Liftvärd

December 2017 - May 2018

+61 436188737

Fredrik Jelk - Järvsöbacken Sweden. +46 705782587

Remi Lövhöjden – Trancher Entrecote. +47 9262257

Andrew Agar - Chalet One France. +44 (0) 7899 911855

Aven Watson – Footscray Milking Station & 6 ways Bistro Melbourne. +61 431782347

Rosa Licciardi - Kin Melbourne. +61 400662602